http://www.christycanyon.com/privacy.php

Last updated on AUGUST 17, 2020.
christycanyon.com is a website owned and operated by Gamma Entertainment Inc., Gamma Billing Inc., and Digigamma B.V.,
and this Privacy Policy applies only to the personal information that Gamma Entertainment Inc. , Gamma Billing Inc.,
and Digigamma B.V. and its subsidiaries and affiliates (collectively, "Company", "Gamma", "we,"
or
"us," or "our") collects
through this website and all other interactive services that we provide, and all of the associated content,
functionalities,
and advertising (collectively, the "Membership Services"). This Privacy Policy governs our Membership Services and
this
website regardless of how and where you access the Memberships Services and this website.
READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY. BY USING OUR MEMBERSHIP SERVICES AND THIS WEBSITE, YOU AGREE TO THE TERMS OF
THIS
PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT USE THE MEMBERSHIP SERVICES
AND
THIS WEBSITE.
THIS WEBSITE AND OUR MEMBERSHIP SERVICES ARE INTENDED FOR ADULTS ONLY AND ARE NOT INTENDED FOR PERSONS UNDER THE AGE
OF
18 YEARS OLD (OR THE APPLICABLE AGE OF MAJORITY IN THE JURISDICTION WHERE OUR MEMBERSHIP SERVICES OR THIS WEBSITE IS
ACCESSED).
1. Collection of your personal information.
1.1 Information you provide to use our Membership Services and this website
Personal information is any information that relates to an identified person or information which, together with
other
information, may identify a person.
We collect any information that you provide during your use of our Membership Services and this website, including
i)
contact information (first and last names); ii) account credentials (username, password, and email address); iii)
payment information (credit card and bank account information) and transaction history, type of device used and
device
fingerprint, and IP address. We also collect information you provide or allow us to access when you do certain
things,
such as:
Enter registration information for one or more of our Membership Services;
Enter a contest or register for a promotion;
Post information, messages or comments in public areas of this website;
Correspondence with Client Relations and information provided to Client Relations;
Make a purchase any of our Membership Services; or
Request certain features (e.g., newsletters, updates, emails, and other products).
You can choose not to provide us or withdraw your consent with certain personal information by contacting Client
Relations but that may result in you being unable to use certain features of our Membership Services because such
information may be required in order for you to register as a member; purchase our Membership Services; participate
in a
contest, promotion, or survey; ask a question or make a comment; or initiate other transactions through our
Membership
Services and this website. If you withdraw your consent to processing the personal information necessary to provide
access to our Membership Services, you may not have access to our Membership Services.
1.2 Information you post on this website
We also collect and retain content, such as comments, that you choose to post to or on any of our Membership
Services
and this website. Other than the information described in Section 1.1, posting content to this website is completely
optional and you may still use our Membership Services and this website without posting any content.
If you use a forum, blog, channel, bulletin board, chat room, user commenting features, or other interactive sharing
or
social features that may be offered through this website, any personal information you submit, disclose, or
otherwise
publish is considered publicly available and can be read, collected, used, and disclosed by other users, by us, and
other third parties. In addition, such postings may appear on other websites and search engines. We are not
responsible
for the control of who reads your posting or what other users may do with the information that you voluntarily post.
Once you have posted information, you may not be able to edit or delete such information if it has been reproduced
on
other websites or shared with third parties outside of our control.
1.3 Payment Information
If you choose to purchase our Membership Services or make any purchase on this website, we will collect information
such
as your credit or debit card information, payment and billing information, and transaction history.
Payment information that you have provided to us shall be shared with our third-party processors in order to
initiate
and complete any purchases on this website. All credit card and bank account transactions and such are processed
with
industry standard encryption through third-party processors who only use your payment information for that purpose.
All
financial data and related personal information will not be shared by us with third parties processors except with
your
authorization or when necessary to carry out all and any transactions requested by you with the understanding that
such
transactions may be subject to rules, terms, conditions and policies of a third-party processors.
We will retain your personal information (including payment information) for a period as determined for legitimate
business requirements including but not limited to legislative compliance, legal, billing and collection purposes.
1.4 Automatically Collected Information
We automatically collect certain information when you use our Membership Services:
Device: We collect information about the device that you use to access or use our Membership Services and
this
website, such as hardware model, operating system, browser information, IP addresses, device fingerprints,
and
other device attributes.
Location information: We collect information about your location, such as general information (e.g., IP
address,
zip code, postal code) and may use that information to customize our Membership Services with location-based
information, advertising, and features.
Usage: We collect information related to the ways in which you interact with our Membership Services and
this
website, such as: referring and exit pages and URLs, platform type, the number of clicks, domain names,
landing
pages, pages and content viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages,
the
date and time you use our Membership Services and this website, the frequency of your use of our Membership
Services and this website, error logs, and other similar information.
As described further below, we may use third-party analytics providers and technologies, including cookies and
similar
tools, to assist in collecting and analyzing the above-mentioned information.
1.5 Cookies, Web Beacons, and other electronic technologies
In general, when you use our Membership Services and this website, we use certain cookies and other similar tracking
technologies to: (a) store your username and password; (b) analyze the usage of our Membership Services and this
website
by collecting the information discussed in Section 1.4 above; (c) customize our Membership Services and this website
to
your preferences; and (d) control the advertising displayed by our Membership Services and this website, as well as
advertisements that may be displayed on this website and on other websites.
We use a variety of cookies, including the following: (a) Analytical cookies which monitor the performance of our
Membership Services and this website and help us provide better products or identify areas needing maintenance; (b)
Tracking cookies are used in relation to those who help promote and advertise our Membership Services and this
website;
(c) Functional/Flash cookies are helpful to record your usage preferences of our Membership Services and this
website
(for example, these cookies track the scenes or photos stored in your favorites' folder, your preferred language,
and
allow 1-click purchasing of our Membership Services); and (d) Advertising cookies or third-party cookies may be used
to
provide specific advertising relevant to you and your usage preferences and interests. As we adopt additional
technologies, we may also gather additional information through other methods.
Please note we cannot control cookies placed on your computer or device by third party advertisers. The cookies may
reflect de-identified information (information that does not identify any individual) linked to or derived from
information you voluntarily have submitted to us. We and our trusted partners, third-party service providers, and
vendors may also use other online technologies, such as Flash technologies, Web beacons or pixel tags, and other
similar
technologies, to deliver or communicate with cookies and track your use of the Membership Services and this website,
as
well as serve you advertisements when you are using our Membership Services and this website.
Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can modify your browser settings to decline certain cookies.
Each
browser (Internet Explorer, Google Chrome, Safari, Firefox, or Opera) provides its own instructions on how to
decline
certain cookies, you can visit each browser and you can receive assistance in managing cookies through browsers
links.
You have the right to opt out of non-essential cookies, such as for analytics or advertising purposes, at any time.
If
you choose to decline or otherwise disable cookies, please note that you may not be able to sign in, customize, or
use
many of the essential and interactive features of our Membership Services and this website.
1.6 Information from Trusted Partner and Other Third Parties
We may obtain additional information about you from our trusted partners and other third parties as described under
Section 1.8 below. We may combine information that we collect from you with information about you that we obtain
from
such trusted partners and other third parties and information derived from any other websites that we own and/or
operate, as well as subscription, or Membership Services that we provide.
1.7 Emails
You shall provide your email address when you sign-up to be a user of this website and purchase our Membership
Services.
We may send you emails on behalf of ourselves, our affiliates, our trusted partners, third-party service providers
and
advertisers. We also may include Web beacons in e-mail communications to determine whether the message has been
opened
and for other analytics.
You may opt-out of receiving promotional emails from us at any time by clicking on the unsubscribe link at the
bottom of
any email, by visiting http://www.td3x.com/ or by contacting Client Relations. It
may
take up to fourteen (14) days for us to process your an opt-out request. Furthermore, you must also directly contact
our
trusted partners, third-party service providers, or third parties from which you receive email communication to
unsubscribe.
You cannot opt-out of receiving emails from us regarding your account information, purchases, orders, receipts, and
other types of transactional and relationship e-mail communications, such as service announcements, administrative
notices, and surveys, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving such emails.
1.8 Information from Other Sources
We also obtain personal information from other third-party sources. We protect this personal information according
to
this Privacy Policy and any additional restrictions imposed by the source of the information received. These sources
may
could include but not limited to: i) payment service providers who provide us with payment information and other
information related to fraud detection/prevention, or updates to that information, based on their relationship with
you;
ii) online and offline data providers, from which we obtain demographic, interest based and online advertising and
sales
related data; or iii) publicly-available sources such as open government databases.
2. Use of your personal information.
We use your personal information that we collect for the following purposes:
How Information is Used
Process your transactions and maintain your account(s)
Type of information:
Payment information
Legal Compliance:
Consent
Required for the performance of a contract with you
Required for compliance legal obligations associated with processing online financial transactions
Required for the purposes of our legitimate interests of providing our Membership Services on this
website
Send you information about your relationship or transactions with us
Type of information:
Contact information
Transaction history
Legal Compliance:
Consent
Required for the performance of a contract with you
Required for compliance legal obligations associated with processing online financial transactions
Required for the purposes of our legitimate interests of providing our Membership Services on this
website
Send you alerts or other communications via email or other media or networks
Type of information:
Contact information
Account preferences
Legal Compliance:
Consent
Required for the performance of a contract with you
Required for the purposes of our legitimate interests of providing our Membership Services on this
website.
Notify you about new features of our Membership Services on this website, special events, or products,
services, sales and special offers with us and third-party partners/affiliates, and browser
notifications
Type of information:
Contact information
Account preferences
Legal Compliance:
Consent
Required for the purposes of our legitimate interests of providing our Membership Services on this
website
Administer contests
Type of information:
Contact information
Account preferences
Legal Compliance:
Consent
Required for the performance of a contract with you
Required for the purposes of our legitimate interests of providing our Membership Services on this
website
Process and respond to your inquiries/questions
Type of information:
Contact information
Legal Compliance:
Consent
Required for the performance of a contract with you
Required for the purposes of our legitimate interests of providing our Membership Services on
this website
Contact you with information that will be of interest to you
Type of information:
Contact information
Account preferences
Legal Compliance:
Consent
Required for the purposes of our legitimate interests of providing our Membership Services on
this
website
Attribute content to you that you make available through our Membership Services (such as comments you
post
on this website)
Type of information:
Contact information
Legal Compliance:
Consent
Required for the purposes of our legitimate interests of providing our Membership Services on this
website
Generate and review reports and data about our users, our Membership Services and website usage
patterns
Type of information:
Device information
Usage information
Location information
Account preferences
Legal Compliance:
Consent
Required for the purposes of our legitimate interests of maintaining and improving our Membership
Services and this website
Perform analytics and research aimed at improving the accuracy, effectiveness, usability, or
popularity
of
our Membership Services and this website
Type of information:
Device information
Usage information
Location information
Account preferences
Legal Compliance:
Consent
Required for the purposes of our legitimate interests of maintaining and improving our Membership
Services and this website
Improve the content and features of our Membership Services and this website or develop new Membership
Services and other services for this website
Type of information:
Device information
Usage information
Location information
Account preferences
Legal Compliance:
Consent
Required for the purposes of our legitimate interests of improving our Membership Services and this
website
Allow for personalized content and advertising and sales that you see on this website and to
understand
how
users interact with and use our advertisements and sales, Membership Services and this
website
Type of information:
Device information
Usage information
Location information
Account preferences
Legal Compliance:
Consent
Required for the purposes of our legitimate interests of providing our Membership Services on this
website
Enforce the legal terms that govern your use of our Membership Services and this website
Type of information:
Location information
Legal Compliance:
Required for the purposes of our legitimate interests of protecting our legal rights
Administer and troubleshoot our Membership Services and this website
Type of information:
Location information
Legal Compliance:
Consent
Required for the performance of a contract with you
Required for the purposes of our legitimate interests of maintaining and improving our Membership
Services and this website
Associate your activities, customize content or tailor advertising across different devices and
browsers
that
you use to access our Membership Services and this website
Type of information:
Device information
Usage information
Location information
Account preferences
Legal Compliance:
Consent
Required for the purposes of our legitimate interests of improving our Membership Services and this
website
For the specific purpose for which you provide information which will be disclosed at the time you
provide
the information
Legal Compliance:
Consent, which will be obtained at the time information is collected
3. Disclosure of your personal information.
We may disclose your personal information for certain purposes and to third parties, as described below:
Third-party Disclosures:
With affiliated, non-affiliated third parties, and trusted third party partners to provide our
Membership
Services or products and sales that may be of interest to you
Type of information:
Type of device used
Legal Compliance:
Consent
Required for the purposes of our legitimate interests of advertising products or our Membership
Services
that may be of interest to you
With third-party service providers or affiliates of our Company in order to provide our Membership
Services
on this website or to communicate with you on our behalf
Type of information:
Web page history
IP address
Email address
Type of device used
Legal Compliance:
Consent
Required for the performance of a contract with you
Required for the purposes of our legitimate interests of advertising our Membership Services and
this website
With third-party service providers or affiliates of our Company in order to provide advertising,
marketing and sales on our behalf
Type of information:
Web page history
IP address
Email address
Type of device used
Legal Compliance:
Consent
Required for the purposes of our legitimate interests of advertising products or our Membership
Services
that may be of interest to you
With our contest advertisers, operators, and/or sponsors when you sign up to participate in a
contest
Type of information:
Email address
Contact information
Copy of personal identification of the winner to verify age restrictions
Legal Compliance:
Consent
Required for the performance of a contract with you
Required for the purposes of our legitimate interests of providing contests
With third parties in response to any subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process we receive, or
to
establish or exercise our legal rights or to defend against legal claims
Type of information:
Any relevant personal information
Legal Compliance:
Required for the purposes of our legitimate interests of complying with the law or protecting our
rights
or the rights of others
Required for the performance of a task carried out in the public interest
Required for compliance with our legal obligations
With third parties with whom we have a contractual relationship for advertising, including without
limitation
third-party advertisers and advertising networks
Legal Compliance:
Consent
Required for the purposes of our legitimate interests of advertising products or Membership Services
that may be of interest to you
With third parties such as law enforcement, government agencies, courts, and/or other organizations
when
we
believe in good faith that a disclosure is appropriate in order to investigate, prevent, or take
action
regarding possible violations of this Privacy Policy you accessed and/or to protect the rights and
property
of our Company, our employees, users and the public
Type of information:
Any relevant personal information
Legal Compliance:
Required for the purposes of our legitimate interests of complying with the law or protecting our
rights
or the rights of others
Required for the performance of a task carried out in the public interest
Required for compliance with our legal obligations
With third parties such as law enforcement, government agencies, courts, and/or other organizations
when
we
believe in good faith that a disclosure is appropriate in order to investigate, prevent, or take
action
regarding possible illegal activities, suspected fraud, or situations involving potential threats to
the
physical safety of any person
Type of information:
Any relevant personal information
Legal Compliance:
Required for the purposes of our legitimate interests of complying with the law or protecting our
rights
or the rights of others
Required for the performance of a task carried out in the public interest
Required for compliance with our legal obligations
With third parties in connection with any proposed or actual merger, reorganization, transfer of
control,
a
sale of some or all our Company assets, or a financing or acquisition of all or a portion of our
business by
another company
Type of information:
Any relevant personal information
Legal Compliance:
Required for the purposes of our legitimate interests of corporate restructuring
Required for compliance with our legal obligations
4. Online analytics and tailored advertising.
4.1 Online analytics
We may use third-party web analytics with our Membership Services and this website, such as those of Google
Analytics.
These service providers use the sort of technology described in Section 1.5 to help us analyze how users use our
Membership Services and this website, including by recording the third-party website from which you arrive prior to
this
website. The information (including but not limited to your IP address, credit card and bank account information for
fraud detection/prevention) collected by the technology will be disclosed to or collected directly by these service
providers, who use the information to evaluate your use of our Membership Services and this website. We also use
Google
Analytics for certain purposes related to advertising, as described under Section 4.2 below.
You have the choice to opt-out of cookies and other technologies t for analytics at any time. To opt-out of Google
Analytics from using your information for analytics, you may install the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on,
please
visit Google.
4.2 Tailored advertising
When you use our Membership Services and this website, we may view advertisements based on various factors such as
the
content of the webpage you are visiting, the personal information you provide to us. These advertisements may be
based
on your current activity or your activity over time and may be tailored to your interests.
You have the choice to opt-out of certain cookies and other technologies that provide you with such tailored
advertising. To opt-out of Google Analytics for display advertising or customize Google display network
advertisements,
you can visit the Google Ads settings webpage. Each operating system (iOS, Android, and Windows/Microsoft) provides
its
own instructions on how to prevent the delivery of tailored in-application advertisements, you can visit each
operating
system website to opt-out. Please note that to the extent advertising technology is integrated into our Membership
Services and this website, you may still receive advertisements even if you opt-out of tailored advertising with
Google
Analytics, but such advertisements may not be tailored specifically to you. Please note that we do not control any
of
the above opt-out links and are not responsible for any choices you make using these mechanisms or the continued
availability or accuracy of these mechanisms.
5. Access your personal information.
You may access and review certain user profile information by logging into this website at the relevant sections
where
such information may be located or by contacting us at Client Relations. You may access and update your password,
photo,
and nickname on your user profile by logging into this website at the relevant sections.
Under certain circumstances, you may have the right to update your payment method, where applicable (For example,
your
credit card has expired, or you wish to change the credit card associated with your purchase to our Membership
Services). In some circumstance, certain user profile information cannot be updated or modified; you must create a
new
user account and purchase a new membership and you are solely responsible for cancelling any initial or duplicate
memberships with our Membership Services. Any such termination shall be subject to our cancellation policy under our
Terms and Conditions of this website.
6. Protection of your personal information.
We have implemented a variety of safeguards including administrative, technical, and physical security measures to
protect against the unauthorized access, disclosure, destruction or alteration of your personal information. We use
some
encryption with the transmission of your personal information, and we use firewalls to protect and protect against
the
unauthorized access. All credit card and bank account transactions and such are processed with industry standard
encryption through third-party processors who only use your payment information for that purpose.
It is always your responsibility to safeguard and keep confidential your login information to our Membership
Services
and this website. Please be advised that we may deactivate any Membership Services or account for abuse if we are of
the
belief that your login information is being used by others and not you.
Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot
guarantee
that information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy.
We may aggregate and/or de-identify your information (information that does not identify any person) and such
information shall not be linked to you personally. Our use and disclosure of such aggregated or de-identified
information is not subject to this Privacy Policy and may be disclosed to others without limitation and for any
purpose.
7. Retention of your personal information.
We will retain your personal information (including payment information) for a period as determined for legitimate
business requirements including but not limited to legislative compliance, legal, billing and collection purposes.
8. Linked websites.
Our Membership Services and this website may contain links to trusted partners, affiliated and non-affiliated
third-party service providers and third-party websites for the purposes of advertisements, sales, and marketing. We
are
not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those trusted partners, affiliated and non-affiliated
third-party service providers and third-party websites.
We have relationships with trusted partners and third-party providers to provide advertisements, sales, marketing,
content, products, services, and functionality through the Membership Services on this website. When you visit
websites
or use any services or products provided in conjunction with one or more of these trusted partners and third-party
providers and the brands of those providers appear on the website or services in connection with such
advertisements,
sales, marketing, content, products, services, and functionality, we share any information you provide or that is
collected during your use of those services with those trusted partners and third-party providers.
In some cases, our trusted partners and third-party providers may collect information from you directly, in which
case
our trusted partners and third-party provider's privacy policy (which may differ from this Privacy Policy) shall
apply.
Some of our trusted partners and third-party providers may use cookies or in conjunction with web beacons or other
tracking technologies to collect information about you when you use our Membership Services and this website. The
information that are collected by our trusted partners and third-party providers may be associated with your
personal information or they may collect information about your
online
activities over time and across different websites and other online services. If you have any questions regarding
the
privacy policy of any of our trusted partners and third-party providers, you should contact the provider directly
for
more information.
9. Location transfer of your personal information.
Personal information captured on this website may be stored in the US and Canada and the personal information
captured
on this website may be transferred to, and stored or otherwise processed at, a destination outside the European
Economic
Area (hereinafter "EEA"), including destinations that are not subject to Data Privacy Provisions equivalent to those
in
the EEA countries in which you provided your personal information. We may transfer your personal information, to any
country in which we or any of our affiliates, subsidiaries, entities that are controlled by, or are under common
control
with us, our trusted partners, or third-party service providers, are located, with your continued use of our
Membership
Services and this website. We shall perform all reasonable procedures required to ensure that your personal
information
is processed and transferred safely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
10. California.
Under the California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA), if you are a resident of the State of California and we are
processing
your personal information, you have the following rights:
Access / Disclosure: You have the right to request a written copy of the information (in digital
format
only) that we hold about you.
Forgotten (Deletion/Eraser): Under certain limited circumstances, you have the right to request that
we
erase from our records the personal information that we hold about you.
Withdrawal Consent: If you have provided consent for the processing of your information you have the
right (in certain circumstances) to withdraw that consent at any time which will not affect the lawfulness
of
the processing before your consent was withdrawn.
Portability: Under certain limited circumstances, you have the right to have the information we hold
about you transferred to another organization or you in a readily useable format.
Right to Opt-Out: You have the right to opt-out of the sale of your information to third parties (to
the
extent applicable) and you may access the "Do not sell my personal information" link provided on this
website to
exercise such right.
Right to Equal Membership Services: You have the right to equal Membership Services and pricing on
this
website.
If you are a resident of the State of California and you wish to exercise any of your rights, please submit your
request
(providing your full account information, identification, and the specific right that you wish exercise) in an email
to
Client Relations at support@famesupport.com.
We shall comply with your request in less than forty-five (45) days, where your request does not prove impossible or
involve disproportionate effort for us to comply. California law permits you to exercise and obtain information from
us
once a year and free of charge.
If you are a resident of the State of California and if you have any questions, comments, or concerns regarding your
rights, please contact us via email to privacy@gammae.com or write to us at
the
following address: Gamma Entertainment Inc., 3300 Boulevard Cote-Vertu, Suite 406, Montreal, Quebec, Canada, H4R
2B7.
Attention: Legal Department - Privacy Policy.
11. Nevada.
Under the Nevada Privacy Laws, if you are a resident of the State of Nevada and we are processing your personal
information, you have the following rights:
Withdrawal Consent: If you have provided consent for the processing of your information you have the
right (in
certain circumstances) to withdraw that consent at any time which will not affect the lawfulness of the
processing before your consent was withdrawn.
Right to Opt-Out: You have the right to opt-out of the sale of your information to third parties (to
the extent
applicable).
If you are a resident of the State of Nevada and you wish to exercise any of your rights, please submit your request
(providing your full account information, identification, and the specific right that you wish exercise) in an email
to
Client Relations at support@famesupport.com.
We shall comply with your request in less than sixty (60) days, free of charge, where your request does not prove
impossible or involve disproportionate effort for us to comply.
If you are a resident of the State of Nevada and if you have any questions, comments, or concerns regarding your
rights,
please contact us via email to privacy@gammae.com or write to us at the
following address: Gamma Entertainment Inc., 3300 Boulevard Cote-Vertu, Suite 406, Montreal, Quebec, Canada, H4R
2B7.
Attention: Legal Department - Privacy Policy.
12. European Union.
Under the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), if you are an EU resident and we are processing your personal
information, you have the following rights:
Access / Disclosure: You have the right to request a copy of the information (in digital format only)
that we hold about you.
Rectification: You have the right to have information that we hold about you that is inaccurate or
incomplete corrected.
Forgotten (Deletion/Eraser): Under certain limited circumstances, you have the right to request that
we
erase from our records the information that we hold about you.
Processing Restrictions: Under certain limited circumstances, you have the right to restrict the
processing of your information.
Withdrawal Consent: If you have provided consent for the processing of your information you have the
right (in certain circumstances) to withdraw that consent at any time which will not affect the lawfulness
of
the processing before your consent was withdrawn.
Portability: Under certain limited circumstances, you have the right to have the information we hold
about you transferred to another organization or you in a readily useable format.
Objection: You have the right to object to certain types of processing of your information such as
direct
marketing (to the extent applicable).
Objection to Automated Processing (including profiling): You have the right to not be subject to the
legal effects of automated processing or profiling.
GDPR applies to the European Union Member States, which includes: Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, Czech
Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Lithuania,
Luxembourg,
Malta, Netherlands, Poland, Portugal, Romania, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, and Sweden. It also includes the United
Kingdom (Channel Isles, England, Northern Ireland, Scotland, and Wales.). Furthermore, GDPR also includes European
Economic Area Countries, such as Iceland, Lichtenstein, and Norway.
If you are an EU resident and you wish to exercise any of your rights, please submit your request (providing your
full
account information, identification, and the specific right that you wish exercise) in an email to Client Relations
at
support@famesupport.com.
We shall comply with your request in less than thirty (30) days, free of charge, where your request does not prove
impossible or involve disproportionate effort for us to comply.
If you are an EU resident and if you have any questions, comments, or concerns regarding your rights, please contact
us
via email to privacy@gammae.com or write to us at the following address:
Gamma
Entertainment Inc., 3300 Boulevard Cote-Vertu, Suite 406, Montreal, Quebec, Canada, H4R 2B7. Attention: Legal
Department
- Data Protection Officer.
13. Canada.
We respect the current federal and provincial privacy laws and regulations in Canada including The Personal
Information
Protection and Electronic Documents Act (PIPEDA) applicable for Manitoba, New Brunswick, Newfoundland and Labrador,
Northwest Territories, Nova Scotia, Nunavut, Ontario, Prince Edward Island, Saskatchewan, and Yukon. Further, we
respect
the current provincial privacy laws of Quebec, An Act Respecting the Protection of Personal Information in the
Private
Sector; British Columbia, Personal Information Protection Act; and Alberta, Personal Information Protection Act.
We will only use your personal information for the purposes intended and as detailed in this Privacy Policy unless
we
have obtained your consent to use it for other purposes.
Residents of Canada are notified that the personal information they provide to us may be stored in Canada, United
States
and/or the Netherlands and may be subject to disclosure to authorized law enforcement or government agencies in
response
to lawful demand under the laws of that country.
If you are a resident of Canada and if you have any questions, comments, or concerns regarding your rights, please
contact us via email to privacy@gammae.com or write to us at the following
address: Gamma Entertainment Inc., 3300 Boulevard Cote-Vertu, Suite 406, Montreal, Quebec, Canada, H4R 2B7.
Attention:
Legal Department - Privacy Policy.
14. Australia.
We respect the current privacy laws and regulations in Australia including Privacy Act 1988 (Act No. 119 of 1988).
We
will only use your personal information for the purposes intended and as detailed in this Privacy Policy unless we
have
obtained your consent to use it for other purposes.
If you are a resident of Australia and if you have any questions, comments, or concerns regarding your rights,
please
contact us via email to privacy@gammae.com or write to us at the following
address: Gamma Entertainment Inc., 3300 Boulevard Cote-Vertu, Suite 406, Montreal, Quebec, Canada, H4R 2B7.
Attention:
Legal Department - Privacy Policy.
15. Brazil.
Under the LGPD (Lei Geral de Proteção de Dados Pessoais), if you are a resident of Brazil and we are processing your
personal information, you have the following rights:
Access / Disclosure: You have the right to request a copy of the information (in digital format only) that we
hold about you.
Rectification: You have the right to have information that we hold about you that is inaccurate or incomplete
corrected.
Forgotten (Deletion/Eraser): Under certain limited circumstances, you have the right to request that we erase
from our records the information that we hold about you.
Processing Restrictions: Under certain limited circumstances, you have the right to restrict the processing of
your information.
Withdrawal Consent: If you have provided consent for the processing of your information you have the right
(in certain circumstances) to withdraw that consent at any time which will not affect the lawfulness of the processing
before your consent was withdrawn.
Portability: Under certain limited circumstances, you have the right to have the information we hold about you
transferred to another organization or you in a readily useable format.
Objection: You have the right to object to certain types of processing of your information such as direct
marketing (to the extent applicable).
If you are a resident of Brazil and you wish to exercise any of your rights, please submit your request (providing your
full account information, identification, and the specific right that you wish exercise) in an email to Client Relations
at support@famesupport.com.
If you are a resident of Brazil and if you have any questions, comments, or concerns regarding your rights, please contact
us via email to privacy@gammae.com or write to us at the following address: Gamma Entertainment Inc., 3300 Boulevard Cote-Vertu,
Suite 406, Montreal, Quebec, Canada, H4R 2B7. Attention: Legal Department - Data Protection Officer.”
16. Third-party rights.
This Privacy Policy does not create rights enforceable by third parties.
17. Minors.
Our Membership Services and this website are not intended for any persons under the age of 18 years old or the
applicable age of majority in the jurisdiction where this website is accessed.
We do not knowingly collect information from minors, and we shall immediately delete and terminate any account if we
become aware that a minor has an account with us. If you become aware that your child has provided us with personal
information, please contact Client Relations immediately. Any such termination shall be subject to our cancellation
policy under our Terms and Conditions of this website.
18. Updates and Corrective Measures.
We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time to reflect changes in the law, our data collection
and
use practices, the features of our Membership Services and this website, or advances in technology. Your continued
use
of our Membership Services and this website following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy will mean you
consent and accept those changes.
We shall not guarantee any error-free performance under this Privacy Policy. We will always use our reasonable
efforts
to comply with this Privacy Policy and shall take corrective action of any failure to comply with this Privacy
Policy.
We shall not be liable for any incidental, consequential or punitive damages relating to this Privacy Policy.
19. Contact Information.
If you have any questions, comments, or concerns regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us via email to privacy@gammae.com or write to us at the following address: Gamma
Entertainment
Inc., 3300 Boulevard Cote-Vertu, Suite 406, Montreal, Quebec, Canada, H4R 2B7. Attention: Legal Department - Privacy
Policy.
